<d:chapter version="5.0" xmlns:d="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
           xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
           xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML">
  <?xml-stylesheet href="../css/style.css" type="text/css"?>
  <?dbhtml filename="the-truth/index.html" ?>
  <d:title> The Truth </d:title>
  <d:sect1>
    <d:title>The Start</d:title>
    <d:para>
      This journey is an important one, the most important of my life as I do not
      know whether I will return or not. Someone like <d:ulink
      url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yuri_Gagarin">Yuri Alekseyevich
      Gagarin</d:ulink>
      would have felt it as the first person going to space. It causes a twister
      in your mind and a tsunami in your gut. However, I must embark on this
      journey as there is no other choice. Since there is no other choice the
      only one must be taken. I calmed my mind that why do you worry about this
      life. There is no one to cry if you die. The world will go on without
      anyone every remembering you, after all they care about the results of your
      actions and not about you as a person or your opinion. You know what
      happened when you had money, and when you lost it.
    </d:para>
    <d:para>
      So now the fear of losing life is gone. Focus returned on task at hand. To
      fix the nonsense of this world I need a hero of highest quality. A champion
      of all times. Who can be such person? To figure that out I asked myself
      what is most important? The answer is survival. Survival is existence and
      existence is truth. Truth is the only thing which exists and eternal. So I
      need a champion of truth. Now it became easy that I need to go to <d:ulink
      url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Harishchandra">Harishchandra</d:ulink>. Only
      Harishchandra is fit to rule and no one else. He must help me.
    </d:para>
    <d:para>
      Now that I have my first destination so I hopped on my time machine and in
      an instant I was with Harishchandra when he had just asked her wife for
      half of her <d:emphasis role="italic">Sari</d:emphasis>(a five yard single
      piece cloth Indian women wear), as funeral charge to burn their son. It was
      painful to watch. I am from an era where duties are ignored and corruption
      is rampant and here is this man asking her own wife for half of what she is
      wearing. Time stood still. I was filled with extreme sorrow for current
      state of earth and at the same time I was joyous that I chose the right
      champion. Never felt like this before. Well, Gods appeared and all that
      happened which you know. As soon as Gods allowed all beings on earth to
      heaven with body I approached Harishchandra. I introduced myself and said
      that your job is not done yet. I am from <d:ulink
      url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kali_Yuga">Kaliyuga</d:ulink> and have
      come seeking his help to prevent humanity from disaster. I asked him that
      he must travel with me on this journey to future, so that mankind must be
      saved from disaster. He readily agreed without hesitation and said that I
      am very brave to have risked my life this way.
    </d:para>
  </d:sect1>
</d:chapter>
