<d:chapter version="5.0" xmlns:d="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
           xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
           xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML">
  <?xml-stylesheet href="../css/style.css" type="text/css"?>
  <?dbhtml filename="the-wisdom/index.html" ?>
  <d:title>The Wisdom </d:title>
  <d:sect1>
    <d:title>Seeking Wisdom</d:title>
    <d:para>
      Now that I have a champion and a wise king I asked him that which other
      person should we take along. He answered he has lived only in <d:ulink
      url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Satya_Yuga">Satya Yuga</d:ulink> and all
      beings are their best in this time. He has not seen other yugas and know other people
      from them. However, we need a person of immense knowledge. With this clue
      it was not hard to decided that we needed <d:ulink
      url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ravana">Ravana</d:ulink>. I told him
      that we need Ravana. I had to tell him all the story of <d:ulink
      url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ramayana">Ramayana</d:ulink>. Since Gods
      were present I asked <d:ulink
      url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vishnu">Lord Vishnu</d:ulink> whether he
      will help us. Lord Vishnu refused. He said that you have free will and as
      Gods they have given intellect and wisdom to us. We should not expect Gods
      for any help. We have already been given what we deserve and will be given
      in future. He also said that Gods will not interfere in kali Yuga at all in
      human actions. That made sense. That also meant that Hanuman and Lord Rama
      are out of question. So we agreed that we need Ravana. Now the problem is
      how and when do we approach him. This is a grave question because he will
      not help easily. Harishchandra told me that since I have the knowledge of
      history I have to find the solution as he does not know future. He also
      said that it is my quest so I got to find a way.
    </d:para>
    <d:para>
      We need a plan to approach him at right time so that Ravana helps us. I needed
      time to make a plan and when you have a time travel machine time is never a
      problem. So to solve this problem I had to ask myself was he born evil?
      No. He was born an innocent child. So why did he follow the evil path? He
      was so learned. The answer is not hard to find. The answer lies in the fact
      that he was discriminated and feared for his knowledge. Due to his
      knowledge and power he became arrogant and chose wrong path. Arroganc of
      power and money cannot be reasoned with. Arrogance of shallow knowledge can
      be eaily broken. However, he was learned and like a truly learned man he
      did not have pride about his knowledge. I knew because he helped Rama his
      arch enemy please Durga for winning the war against him. He very well knew
      that if does not choose evil path he will not die and remain immortal. So
      he chose to die at the hands of God. However, this was an opportunity to
      also fix the whole Sita kidnapping and save all who died. Also, we may
      need Bali and others so I decided to approach him when he completes his
      education and has not acquired any powers from Gods yet. So we hopped on
      our time machine for <d:ulink
      url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Treta_Yuga">Treta Yuga</d:ulink>.
    </d:para>
    <d:sect2>
      <d:title>The Argument</d:title>
      <d:para>
        And with a boom we arrived to Ravana as he had just completed his
        education and coming out of <d:ulink
        url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gurukula">Gurukula</d:ulink>. I am
        no coward but facing Ravana was an uphill task. He was shining in the
        prime of his youth. The life of gurukul had him appear like a living
        God. I was nervous but the presence of Harishchandra gave me the
        courage to face him. I also gave myself a bit of boost with the fact
        that even Ravana does not know what will happen in future but I do. So
        the plan is cooked and ready for execution.
      </d:para>
      <d:para>
        Ravana saw us and he was surprised to see me with my funny modern dress
        of half pant and a T-shirt. We approached and greeted him. He greeted
        back. Before we could say a thing he asked along with the greeting as to who we are and why am I dressed like that? I
        replied with my name that I am from future(Kali yuga) and my comapnion is Harishchandra from Satya Yuga. To which he asked
        how is it possible that two persons from different yugas are in Treta yuga and what are we doing there? I told him about
        the time machine and the purpose to fix Kali yuga and humans in Kali yuga. I said that we need his help in fixing humans in
        Kali yuga.
      </d:para>
    </d:sect2>
  </d:sect1>
</d:chapter>
